georgebrown.ca 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy

_George Brown College (George Brown) is collecting the personal information requested under the authority of and for activities authorized by the Ontario Colleges of Applied Arts and Technology Act, 2002._

_This information will only be used by George Brown or its agents for the purposes specified and will not be sold or otherwise disclosed._

_If you have any questions or concerns related to Freedom of Information (FOI) and Protection of Privacy, please contact the FOI Coordinator for the college at 416-415-5000, ext. 4646._

## George Brown College>Web Privacy Policy

Respecting the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information is important to George Brown College. This Website Privacy Policy explains how George Brown College collects, uses and discloses your personal information on the George Brown College website (the “Website”).

The purpose of this Policy is to make visitors to this Website aware of how George Brown College protects the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information and the circumstances under which George Brown College uses your personal information.

### **Jurisdiction**

The terms and conditions under which you use this Website (including as it relates to this privacy policy) are governed by and interpreted solely in accordance with the laws of the Province of Ontario and no other jurisdiction. You are responsible for informing yourself of the laws of the jurisdiction and complying with those laws. Any litigation relating to the terms and conditions of use of this Website (including as it relates to this privacy policy) shall be brought solely within the Province of Ontario and shall be within the exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of the Province of Ontario.

### **What is personal information?**

Personal information is information about an identifiable individual, not including business contact information (i.e. information that would allow an individual to be contacted at their place of business, or work product information). For example, personal information includes such things as your name, date of birth, personal e-mail address, credit card information and other financial information about you.

### **What are the purposes for collection, use and disclosure of personal information?**

George Brown College collects, uses and discloses your personal information with your knowledge and consent and only for purposes that we have identified prior to or at the time we collect the information. Some of the purposes for which George Brown College may collect, use and disclose your personal information on this Website are:

  * To facilitate communication with you
  * To grant you/enable you to access certain special features or areas of the Website 
  * To process any of your requests for information
  * To make available to you through the Website certain services
  * To permit you to subscribe to an E-mail List to receive information
  * To administer participation in contests
  * To announce special events

George Brown College will not sell, trade, lend or otherwise voluntarily disclose to any third parties any personal information that you have provided to us for any purpose not identified under this Privacy Policy. George Brown College may share your personal information with third parties to assist us to administer activities on this Website, such as for website administration and maintenance, administration of contests and data processing, to our professional advisors or otherwise for legitimate and reasonable purposes for which we have obtained your prior consent.

In certain circumstances, George Brown College may disclose your personal information to a government institution that has asserted its lawful authority to obtain the information or where we have reasonable grounds to believe the information could be used in the investigation of an unlawful activity, or to comply with a subpoena or warrant or an order made by a court, person or body with jurisdiction to compel production of information or to comply with court rules regarding a production of records and information, or to our own legal counsel.

When you provide George Brown College with your personal information, such as to sign up to receive emails about our activities or participate in a contest, you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information for these purposes in accordance with the principles that are outlined in the Privacy Policy.

If you have provided your consent and are receiving emails, you may at any time withdraw your consent by changing your preferences and unsubscribing.

### **Use of technology on the website**

The Website uses cookie technology to make your use of the Website more convenient. A cookie is a text file which enables the Website to store any information about your activities on the Website or the length of your stay. If you choose to disable cookies associated with the Website, this may affect your use of the Website and your ability to access certain features of the Website. 

We also log visits to the Website. Our logs include data about visitors’ operating systems, web browser types and information about how users entered our site (e.g., search terms and links) and what users do on the Website. We use this data to understand how our website is located and used and to plan for future enhancements of our website. We log this information by IP address and, if you subscribe to one of our web based accounts, by your account.

### **E-mail list**

The Website allows you to provide us with your e-mail address in order that we may send you information and updates about George Brown College. In order to administer the E-mail List we will collect your name, e-mail address, geographical location, school or work status and areas of interest for communication purposes.

### **E-mail to a friend**

The Website may periodically allow you to provide an e-mail address of a friend and personal information about your friend. The Website will send new stories, links, e-cards, or other information to the friend’s e-mail address. We will assume that, to the extent that we are provided the e-mail address of your friends, you have the consent of your friend to provide us with their e-mail address. We will also assume that you have consented to the friend having your e-mail address. In order to administer this option, we may collect your name, e-mail address, any comments that you provide, as well as the e-mail address of your friend.

### **Job Opportunities**

The Website allows you to submit an application for employment and your resume. The Website will be integrated with an electronic resume management system accessible to our human resources personnel. To administer the resume management system, we will collect your name, address and other information relating to your employment application including information regarding your education, work history and other qualifications.

### **Links to other sites**

The Website contains links to other websites. When you click on of those links, you are connecting to an internet resource external to the George Brown College servers. George Brown College has no responsibility or liability for, or control over those Websites, or internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. Please refer to the privacy policy and terms of use contained in any linked site you choose to go to, and familiarize yourself with that Website’s terms and conditions of use.

### **How do we protect your personal information?**

The Website endeavours to maintain appropriate procedural and technological measures and storage facilities to prevent any unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal information. We exercise care in the secure transmission of your information, however no transmission of information over the internet is one hundred percent secure. We cannot guarantee that information disclosed through the internet cannot be intercepted by third parties. However, George Brown College takes all reasonable precautions available to protect any personal information that is provided to it through the Website including, disposal or destruction of this information.

### **Contacting us about your privacy**

You may request access to your personal information and information about our collection, use and disclosure of information by contacting us at [website@georgebrown.ca](mailto:website@georgebrown.ca). George Brown College attempts to keep records as accurate and complete as possible. You can help us maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying us of any changes to your personal information.

This version of the Web Privacy Policy has been in effect since June 2009. This Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time at our sole discretion and without any prior notice. New versions of this Privacy Policy will be posted here. Your continued use of this Website, subsequent to any changes to the Privacy Policy, will signify that you consent to George Brown College's collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this or any revised Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions around Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy, you may contact our Freedom of Information & Privacy Coordinator at the following address:[odosis@georgebrown.ca](mailto:odosis@georgebrown.ca).
